♪Holding hands silently as flowers fall and winds rise♪
♪يمسك الأيدي بصمت بينما تتساقط الزهور وترتفع الرياح♪
♪Dark tresses cascade like mountains. Dreams intertwine♪
♪خصلات داكنة تتدلى كالجبال. تتشابك الأحلام♪
♪Painting realms, clouds in palm, my brushwork for you♪
♪رسم العوالم، السحب في راحة اليد، فرشاتي لك♪
♪Light and shadow overlap my name across time and space♪
♪يتداخل الضوء والظل مع اسمي عبر الزمان والمكان♪
♪Across starry rivers, I chase dreams afar♪
♪عبر الأنهار المرصعة بالنجوم، أطارد الأحلام البعيدة♪
♪Arms spread wide, falling through heaven and earth♪
♪أذرع مفتوحة على مصراعيها، تسقط عبر السماء والأرض♪
♪The rhythm of breath and heartbeat♪
♪إيقاع التنفس ونبض القلب♪
♪A meeting of the souls♪
♪لقاء الأرواح♪
♪Through shifting seas and lands, I'd know you still♪
♪من خلال البحار والأراضي المتغيرة، سأظل أعرفك♪
♪Eyes bright as moonlit skies, untouched by worldly dust♪
♪عيون لامعة مثل سماء مضاءة بالقمر، غير متأثرة بغبار العالم♪
♪Smiling gazes write eternity♪
♪النظرات المبتسمة تكتب الخلود♪
=The Crush=
=السحق=
=Episode 10= (Resurrection and Undying Devotion)
=الحلقة 10= (القيامة والتفاني الأبدي)
My lady, you're finally awake.
سيدتي، لقد استيقظت أخيرا.
Thankfully, you're okay.
لحسن الحظ أنك بخير.
If something had happened to you,
إذا حدث لك شيء،
I wouldn't have known what to do.
لم أكن أعرف ماذا أفعل.
How did I get back here?
كيف عدت إلى هنا؟
The yamen officers brought you back.
لقد أعادك ضباط اليمان.
Where is Zixuan?
أين زيكسوان؟
He...
هو...
He's...
إنه...
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
In the courtyard.
في الفناء.
Madam.
سيدتي.
Foam in his nose and mouth.
رغوة في أنفه وفمه.
A blood clot on the neck.
جلطة دموية في الرقبة.
He died from drowning.
لقد مات غرقا.
Drowning?
غرق؟
He's drowned?
لقد غرق؟
Yes.
نعم.
Madam.
سيدتي.
He looked for you
لقد بحث عنك
with worry.
مع القلق.
When he reached the riverbank,
وعندما وصل إلى ضفة النهر،
he jumped into the river.
قفز في النهر.
He pulled you out of it,
لقد أخرجك منه
but he sank down.
ولكنه غرق.
Madam.
سيدتي.
This matter remains unclear.
لا تزال هذه المسألة غير واضحة.
Considering it's kidnapping,
بالنظر إلى أنها عملية اختطاف،
I'll treat it as a homicide case.
سأعاملها كقضية قتل.
The body
الجسم
will be taken to the morgue.
سيتم نقله إلى المشرحة.
Take it away.
خذها بعيدا.
Young Master!
سيدي الشاب!
He's gone.
لقد رحل.
Young Master.
السيد الشاب.
Who will make the Top Tea with me?
من سيصنع الشاي معي؟
Madam.
سيدتي.
In my opinion,
في رأيي،
Zixuan's death might actually
قد يكون موت زيكسوان في الواقع
be advantageous for you.
أن يكون مفيدًا لك.
What are you implying?
ماذا تقصد؟
With Zixuan drowned,
مع غرق زيكسوان،
Wei Xiaotang simply needs to remarry
وي شياوتانغ يحتاج فقط إلى الزواج مرة أخرى
to be as effective as
لتكون فعالة مثل
making the Top Tea.
صنع الشاي الأفضل.
- Young Master. - You're an NPC?
- سيدي الشاب. - أنت شخصية غير قابلة للعب؟
Madam.
سيدتي.
Your mission has become much simpler.
أصبحت مهمتك أسهل بكثير.
Young Master.
السيد الشاب.
All I need is to remarry,
كل ما أحتاجه هو الزواج مرة أخرى،
and I can complete the mission?
وأستطيع إكمال المهمة؟
Just remarry.
فقط تزوج مرة أخرى.
- Young Master. - Just remarry.
- سيدي الشاب. - فقط تزوج مرة أخرى.
Young Master.
السيد الشاب.
My lady.
سيدتي.
Just remarry.
فقط تزوج مرة أخرى.
Young Master.
السيد الشاب.
(Spare me your righteous)
(وفر لي صالحك)
(posturing.)
(التظاهر.)
(In this world,)
(في هذا العالم)
(everything can be traded)
(كل شيء يمكن تداوله)
(to get what we want.)
(للحصول على ما نريد.)
(Are we truly allies?)
(هل نحن حلفاء حقا؟)
(I help you secure the position as head of the Li family,)
(أساعدك في تأمين منصب رئيس عائلة لي)
(and you help me win the Top Tea title.)
(وأنت تساعدني في الفوز بلقب أفضل شاي.)
(So, our relationship)
(علاقتنا إذن)
(is all about a deal?)
(كل شيء يتعلق بالصفقة؟)
(Li Zixuan.)
(لي زيكسوان.)
(Why are you being so stubborn?)
(لماذا أنت عنيد هكذا؟)
(Don't fixate on trifles.)
(لا تركز على الأشياء التافهة.)
(This is not a trifle.)
(هذا ليس تافهاً.)
(It's a dirty trick.)
(إنها خدعة قذرة.)
(Anyway,)
(على أي حال،)
(we are connected by contract marriage.)
(نحن مرتبطون بعقد الزواج.)
(Don't pretend we're in love.)
(لا تتظاهر بأننا في حالة حب.)
(My goal is to win the Top Tea title.)
(هدفي هو الفوز بلقب أفضل شاي.)
(If I fail, I can't return home.)
(إذا فشلت، لن أتمكن من العودة إلى المنزل.)
(Then stay with me)
(ثم ​​ابقى معي)
(until we win the Top Tea title.)
(حتى نفوز بلقب أفضل شاي.)
(Making the Top Tea with you)
(صنع الشاي الأفضل معك)
(still holds promise.)
(لا يزال يحمل الوعد.)
(Xiaotang is my wife.)
(شياوتانغ هي زوجتي.)
(From now on, anyone in the household)
(من الآن فصاعدا، أي شخص في المنزل)
(must respect Xiaotang.)
(يجب احترام Xiaotang.)
(You hear me?)
(هل تسمعني؟)
Li Zixuan is dead.
مات لي Zixuan.
Wei Xiaotang just needs to remarry
وي شياوتانغ يحتاج فقط إلى الزواج مرة أخرى
to complete the mission.
لإكمال المهمة.
In that case,
في هذه الحالة،
my mission has actually become simpler.
لقد أصبحت مهمتي في الواقع أبسط.
Good.
جيد.
This way,
من هنا،
I can return home
أستطيع العودة إلى المنزل
and leave this place earlier.
واترك هذا المكان مبكرا.
(Li's Tea Estate)
(مزرعة شاي لي)
Tang, you've suffered so much.
تانغ، لقد عانيت كثيرًا.
I'll take you home right now.
سأوصلك إلى المنزل الآن.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I will
أنا سوف
find you a better husband.
أجد لك زوجًا أفضل.
If you don't wish to remarry,
إذا كنت لا ترغب في الزواج مرة أخرى،
you can stay at home.
يمكنك البقاء في المنزل.
I'll support you.
سأدعمك.
Madam.
سيدتي.
Ning An.
نينغ آن.
I came
لقد جئت
to bid you farewell.
لأقول لك وداعا.
Ning An,
نينغ آن,
stand up and talk.
قف وتحدث.
Madam.
سيدتي.
Since I was a child,
منذ أن كنت طفلا،
I've served Young Master.
لقد خدمت السيد الشاب.
Now that he's gone,
الآن بعد أن رحل،
I must leave too.
يجب علي أن أغادر أيضاً.
I came
لقد جئت
to bid you farewell.
لأقول لك وداعا.
Enough.
كافٍ.
Ning An,
نينغ آن,
stop kneeling and get up now.
توقف عن الركوع وانهض الآن.
Stand up and talk.
قف وتحدث.
After we leave,
بعد أن نغادر،
take good care of yourself.
اعتني بنفسك جيدا.
We're leaving.
نحن نغادر.
Madam, there's one thing.
سيدتي، هناك شيء واحد.
This is what Young Master gave to me
هذا ما أعطاني إياه السيد الشاب
before saving you.
قبل أن أنقذك.
He ordered me to give it to you
لقد أمرني أن أعطيك إياه
no matter what happened.
مهما حدث.
(Contract)
(عقد)
Get in the carriage.
ادخل إلى العربة.
I have to go.
يجب على  أن أذهب.
Madam.
سيدتي.
Take care, Madam.
اعتني بنفسك سيدتي.
(Li's Tea Estate)
(مزرعة شاي لي)
Wait!
انتظر!
Get in!
أدخل!
Tang.
تانغ.
(Today, Li Zixuan and Wei Xiaotang made a contract.)
(اليوم، أبرم Li Zixuan وWei Xiaotang عقدًا.)
(The terms are as follows:)
(الشروط هي كما يلي:)
(Wei Xiaotang shall help Li Zixuan secure the family business.)
(سيساعد Wei Xiaotang Li Zixuan في تأمين أعمال العائلة.)
(In return, Li Zixuan shall)
(في المقابل، يجب على Li Zixuan)
(entrust Wei Xiaotang)
(تكليف وي شياو تانغ)
(with the management of the tea estate.)
(مع إدارة مزرعة الشاي.)
(Wei Xiaotang's authority shall be absolute in all matters.)
(يجب أن تكون سلطة وي شياوتانغ مطلقة في جميع الأمور.)
(No objections allowed.)
(لا يسمح بالاعتراضات.)
(Upon claiming the title of Top Tea,)
(عند المطالبة بلقب أفضل شاي)
(Li Zixuan shall get closer with Wei Xiaotang.)
(يجب أن يقترب Li Zixuan من Wei Xiaotang.)
(Morgue)
(المشرحة)
Xiaotang,
شياو تانغ،
what brings you here?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
I need you to revive Li Zixuan.
أريدك أن تعيد إحياء لي زيكسوان.
Xiaotang,
شياو تانغ،
if I may be blunt,
إذا سمحت لي أن أكون صريحا،
remarrying would be an easier path.
الزواج مرة أخرى سيكون الطريق الأسهل.
Save your concern for me.
احتفظ بقلقك من أجلي.
I need you to revive Li Zixuan.
أريدك أن تعيد إحياء لي زيكسوان.
Alright. Don't regret this choice.
حسنًا، لا تندم على هذا الاختيار.
Just for the record,
فقط للتسجيل،
my method works only once.
طريقتي تعمل مرة واحدة فقط.
Are you certain about it?
هل أنت متأكد من ذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
The buds down the hill soak in the shallow stream.
تنقع البراعم أسفل التل في الجدول الضحل.
The sandy path under the shade of the trees is clean.
المسار الرملي تحت ظلال الأشجار نظيف.
Evening rains patter as cuckoos sing.
تهطل الأمطار في المساء بينما تغني طيور الوقواق.
Who claims youth cannot be reclaimed?
من يدعي أن الشباب لا يمكن استعادته؟
See the stream before my door flow westward!
انظر إلى النهر أمام بابي يتدفق غربًا!
Don't lament the swift passage of time in your old age.
لا تحزن على مرور الوقت السريع في شيخوختك.
My lady, you're finally awake.
سيدتي، لقد استيقظت أخيرا.
My lady.
سيدتي.
Li Zixuan!
لي زيكسوان!
Foam in his nose and mouth.
رغوة في أنفه وفمه.
A blood clot on the neck. He died from drowning.
جلطة دموية في الرقبة. مات غرقًا.
Drowning?
غرق؟
He's not dead yet!
إنه لم يمت بعد!
Well...
حسنًا...
Young Master...
السيد الشاب...
Li Zixuan!
لي زيكسوان!
You can't die!
لا يمكنك أن تموت!
Wake up!
استيقظ!
Our contract remains unfulfilled!
عقدنا لا يزال غير مكتمل!
You are not allowed to die!
لا يجوز لك الموت!
You mustn't die!
لا يجب أن تموت!
My mission isn't done yet!
مهمتي لم تنتهي بعد!
Do you hear me?
هل تسمعني؟
Li Zixuan!
لي زيكسوان!
He is awake!
إنه مستيقظ!
Li Zixuan.
لي زيكسوان.
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
Thank heavens.
الحمد لله.
They say that when husband and wife are united,
يقولون أنه عندما يكون الزوج والزوجة متحدين،
anything can be done.
يمكن فعل أي شيء.
It must be my lady's love
لا بد أن يكون حب سيدتي
for Mr. Li that worked miracles.
للسيد لي الذي صنع المعجزات.
That's why Mr. Li came back to life.
ولهذا السبب عاد السيد لي إلى الحياة.
This is simply miraculous!
هذا أمر معجزة بكل بساطة!
Yes.
نعم.
Young Master.
السيد الشاب.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
My pleasure.
من دواعي سروري.
You scared us.
لقد اخافتنا.
I didn't expect your rescue method
لم أتوقع طريقة الإنقاذ الخاصة بك
to be straight out of a romantic drama.
أن تكون مباشرة من الدراما الرومانسية.
Young Master, how are you feeling now?
سيدي الشاب، كيف تشعر الآن؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.